Step 1: scroll  [OK]\NI can see the Spotify web player interface. The current view shows 'Trending songs', 'Popular artists', and 'Popular alb
Step 2: scroll  [OK]\NI can see the Spotify web player interface. The current view shows 'Popular artists', 'Popular albums and singles', and
Step 3: scroll  [OK]\NI can see the Spotify web player interface. The current view shows 'Popular artists', 'Popular albums and singles', and
Step 4: scroll  [OK]\NI can see the Spotify web player interface. The screen shows 'Popular artists', 'Popular albums and singles', and 'Popul
Step 5: scroll  [OK]\NI can see the Spotify web player interface. The screen shows 'Popular artists', 'Popular albums and singles', and 'Popul
Step 6: click (571, 735) [OK]\NI can see the Spotify web player interface. The screen shows 'Popular artists', 'Popular albums and singles', and 'Popul
Step 7: click (729, 180) [OK]\NI can see the Spotify web player is currently showing an album page for 'Attitude' by Mrs. GREEN APPLE. The screen shows
Step 8: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Spotify web player interface. The screen shows 'Trending songs' at the
Step 9: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Spotify web player interface. The screen shows 'Trending songs' at the
Step 10: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Spotify web player interface. The screen shows 'Trending songs' at the
Step 11: click (727, 226) [OK]\NI can see the Spotify web player interface. The screen shows 'Trending songs' at the top, 'Popular artists' in the middl
Step 12: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Spotify web player interface. The screen shows 'Trending songs' at the